choiceperformance.com 2011-01-28

# Live Out Loud Privacy Policy

The privacy practices of this policy apply to our services available under the domain and subdomains of www.liveoutloud.com as well as the following related websites: www.loralsbigtable.com, www.millionairemakerbook.com, www.getrealwealthcoaching.com, www.liveoutloudcoaching.com, www.lorallangemeier.com, www.TeamMadeMillionaire.com, assets.liveoutloud.com, www.liveoutloudcommunity.com and www.wealthdiva.com (the “Website”). By visiting this Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access the Website.

We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use our services related to the Website, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard use of the Website.

**Information We Collect**  
You can browse the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, billing information, shipping information and other personal information. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature.

For every visitor, we automatically collect and store: the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access the Website; and the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to our sites. We use this information only as anonymous aggregate data to determine the number of visitors to different sections of the Website, to ensure the Website is working properly, and to help us make the Website more useful. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Website. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. We do not install, download or otherwise distribute or utilize Spyware on the Website.

**How We Use Information We Collect**  
We do not sell, rent, trade or otherwise share any personally identifiable information about our users to any third party. This includes, but is not limited to the names, addresses, e-mail addresses, and phone numbers of our users. In addition, we will not disclose any personally identifiable financial or security-related personally identifiable information. We may share the personal information you provide with other companies we have hired to provide services for us. These companies, our vendors, are contractually bound to use personal information we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide. We will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are required by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances (for example, to protect your account from fraud).

**Email**  
Any information that is submitted to us via email becomes our property and may be used at our discretion. The information you send to us may be stored and used to improve the Website and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded.

**Cookies**  
Upon your first visit to the Website, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit most websites. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. We do this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people search. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features or services of this Website may not function properly without cookies.

**SecurityMeasures**  
Your information is stored on servers located in the United States. We use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption and firewalls to protect the transmission of the information you submit to us when you use our secure online forms. The information you provide to us is stored securely. However, even the most robust security systems are not foolproof and users should consider this when revealing any personally identifiable information to any party over any form of media.  
Email that you send us is not necessarily secure against interception. If your email communication includes sensitive information like your Social Security number, your bank account number, or your credit or charge card numbers, contact us through one of our secure online forms or by mail or telephone.

**Children**  
We do not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use the Website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Credit Service Provider**  
We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

**Communication**  
you have any questions about this privacy statement, or our privacy practices, you can contact the company by sending a letter to:

Live Out Loud  
P.O. Box 36  
Zephyr Cove, NV 89448

**Changes**  
Our business changes regularly; this privacy statement will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the privacy and security statement in effect at the time of collection. You should check this policy frequently to see recent changes.
